goodwill.org 2016-10-14

# Privacy Statement | Goodwill Industries International, Inc.

## Privacy Statement

#### Our General Policy

Goodwill Industries International (GII) recognizes the importance of protecting information we may collect from visitors to our site. Our policy is to use the information we acquire from visitors to our sites for internal purposes only, and we maintain appropriate security measures to keep this information private. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.

Users can visit the site without revealing any information about themselves. If one chooses to give us personal information via the Internet for the purposes of correspondence, then it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information.

If users tell us that they do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact, we will respect those wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it. We do not share information web users provide with third parties for commercial purposes.

GII takes precautions to keep the user information disclosed to us secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of information, all personal data is transmitted via a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and access to personal data is restricted via a username and password authentication process. Only authorized GII employees are permitted to access personally identifiable information, and the authorized individuals may do so only for specific work related purposes. GII strives to protect your personal information; however, we urge you to take every precaution when you are on the internet. To better protect your information, be sure to change your passwords often and use a combination of upper and lower case letters, numbers, and special characters.

If users have questions about the types of information collected on this web site or would like to request a correction of any information collected, then please contact us at [contactus@goodwill.org. ](mailto:contactus@goodwill.org?subject=Questions%20about%20Personal%20Information)

#### Use of Cookies

Certain sections of the GII web site use “cookies” to store user information. A cookie is a small string of text that a web site can send to your browser. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your e-mail address. Cookies help us understand which parts of our web sites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to analyze traffic patterns so we can improve the site.

Cookies were originally designed to help a web site distinguish a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. If you are just browsing www.goodwill.org, a cookie identifies only your browser but you do not have to accept the cookie to continue browsing the site. It is possible to set your browser to inform you when a cookie is being placed – then you have the opportunity to decide whether to accept the cookie.

#### User Agreement

If you have any questions about this User Agreement, contact Goodwill Industries International (GII). If you do not agree with these terms of this User Agreement, you may not use the site. GII reserves the right to change this User Agreement at any time without notice.

**LAST UPDATED** : FEBRUARY 10, 2015
